Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Information Center Records, 1901-2005 and undated RL.11121
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 2018 Additions, 1901-2006 and undated; 1
  - Numbered Research Reports, 1919-1988 and undated; 10
    - X2.2-10-AB. JWT Point of View on Copy Testing, 1973 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-11-AB. Review of Techniques and Methods for Testing Advertising Executions, 1978 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-12-AB. On-Air: Are We Testing the Message or the Medium?, 1977 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-13-ABC. Review of Advertising Copy Testing Techniques and Services, 1983 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-14-A. Rough vs. Finished Testing, 1983 (Box R9)
    - X2.2-15-A. Reliability: ARS Persuasion and Recall Measures, 1987 (Box R9)
    - X2.3-4-A. Validity of Current Methods Used for Measuring the Reading of Magazine Advertising, 1944 (Box R9)
    - X2.3-5-A. Analysis of a Study of Printed Advertising Rating Methods, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-5.1. Study of Printed Advertising Rating Methods, 1957 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-5.2-A. Analysis of Printed Advertising Rating Methods, 1958 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-6-A. Study of Readership of Bleed vs. Non-bleed Advertisements, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-6.1. Is There a Case for Bleed?, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-7-A. Study of Food Advertising Readership, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-8. Mock Readership Survey, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-9-A. Starch Magazine Advertisement Readership Service, 1960 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-10. MRCA Media Service, 1960 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-11-AB. Review of Magazine Audience Measurement Services, 1963 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-11.3-A. Analysis of Starch Readership Data--Automobile Advertising, 1968 (Box R10)
    - X2.3-12-A. Overview of Campbell-Mithun Food Service Readership Study, 1976 (Box R10)
    - X2.4-1-A. Effectiveness of Repeated Advertisements, 1956 (Box R10)
    - X2.4-2-ABC. Studies and Material Relating to Advertising Continuity and Frequency, 1959 (Box R10)
    - X2.4-3-A. Flighting vs. Continuity in Television Scheduling, undated (Box R10)
    - X2.6-1-A. Television and Radio Evaluation Through Group Interaction, 1958 (Box R10)
    - X2.6-2. Leading Television Commercial Evaluating Services, 1959 (Box R10)
    - X2.6-3. Audience Size Comparison Between TV Diary and Nielsen Ratings, 1960 (Box R10)
    - X2.6-4-A. Measuring the Advertising Impact of a Television Program, 1960 (Box R10)
    - X2.6-5. OATS: On-Air System for Testing Commercial Effectiveness, 1962 (Box R10)
    - X2.6-6-A. Medium vs. the Message, 1979 (Box R11)
    - X2.6-7-A. People Meter Preliminary Tracking, 1987 (Box R11)
    - X2.6-8-A. People Meters: Where Do We Stand?, 1987 (Box R11)
    - X2.7-1. Color Influence in Advertising, 1961 (Box R11)
    - X2.7-2-ABC. Pre-Teens Reactions to Project Straight Dope (anti-drug PSA), 1970 (Box R11)
    - X3-3-A. Report on Growth in Advertising Competition, 1958 (Box R11)
    - X3-4. Audience Behavior and Advertising, 1957 (Box R11)
    - X3-5. Audience Behavior and the Advertising Medium, 1957 (Box R11)
    - X3-6-AB. Television and Magazines as Complementary Advertising Media, 1959 (Box R11)
    - X3-6.1. Brand Share Requirements, 1960 (Box R11)
    - X3-7. Significant New Developments in Media, 1962 (Box R11)
    - X3-8-AB. Simmons/TGI, 1973 (Box R11)
    - X3-9-AB. Impact of New Media Developments Within a Changing Market Environment, 1981 (Box R11)
    - X3.2-28. General Review of the Magazine Medium, 1954 (Box R11)
    - X3.2-29. General Review of Sunday Newspaper Sections, 1954 (Box R11)
    - X3.2-30-A. Unduplicated Audience of Combinations of Magazines, undated (Box R11)
    - X3.2-31. Analysis of Sunday Newspaper Comic Section, undated (Box R11)
    - X3.2-32-A. Report on Sunday Supplements, 1957 (Box R11)
    - X3.2-33. Report on Magazines, 1957 (Box R11)
    - X3.2-34. Report on Sunday Supplements, 1957 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-34.1-A. Grocery Store Magazines, 1958 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-35-A. Evaluation of Two Types of Consumer Studies Conducted by Print Media, 1960 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-36. Report on Magazines as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-37. Report on Sunday Comics and Magazine Supplements as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-38. Analysis of Store-Distributed Magazines, 1957 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-38.1-A. Test on the Influence of a Vehicle on the Perception of an Advertisement, undated (Box R12)
    - X3.2-38.2-A. Women's Service Magazines, 1962 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-39-ABC. Analysis of Life-Nowland Study, 1963 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-40-ABC. Attitudes of Agency Media Planners Toward Magazines and Magazine Representatives, 1974 (Box R12)
    - X3.2-41-A. Magazine Merchandising Opportunities, 1987 (Box R12)
    - X3.3-3-A. Extent of Reading of Retail Grocery Advertising, 1935 (Box R12)
    - X3.3-4. Report on Newspapers as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R12)
    - X3.3-5-ABC. Size of a Newspaper Ad, 1965 (Box R12)
    - X3.4-1-AB. Description of Three Poster Rating Services, 1957 (Box R12)
    - X3.4-2. Report on Outdoor as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R13)
    - X3.4-3-A. Visibility Achieved by Outdoor Advertising, 1983 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-4.4. Evaluation of Network Television Rating Services, 1958 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-4.5-ABC. Television Programs and Their Advertising Value, 1959 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-4.51. Pond's Television Commercial Test, 1958 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-4.52. Scotties Television Advertising Test, 1958 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-4.6. Report on Television as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-5-ABC. How Some Food Advertisers Schedule Commercials on Network Television, 1959 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-6. Television Ratings and the Audiences for Television Commercials, 1963; 2 folders (Box R13)
    - X3.5-6.1. Study of the Attention Paid to Television Commercials, 1960 (Box R13)
    - X3.5-7. Measuring the Advertising Impact of a Television Program, 1960 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-8-ABC. Study of Six Daytime Television Programs as Commercial Vehicles, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-9-ABC. Effectiveness of Television Commercials, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-10. New Method of Classifying Television Programs, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-11. Performer Popularity Analysis, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-12. Recent Pioneering Research, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-12.1. Evaluation of Adult Daytime Television, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-13. Lever Television Commercial Testing, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-14. Television Program Image Study, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-15. Manual of Television Basics, 1958; 3 folders (Box R14)
    - X3.5-16. Factors Related to Commercial Effect, 1961 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-16.1. JWT Chicago Policy on Evaluation of Television Commercials, 1964 (Box R14)
    - X3.5-17. Instant Chase & Sanborn On-Air Test, 1964 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-18-ABC. Review of Available Published Data on Color Television, 1966 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-19-ABC. Television Commercial Longevity, 1968 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-20. Determining the Effective Life of Television Commercials, 1968 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-21-AB. JWT CATV Commercial Testing System, 1969 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-22-A. Look at Network Television Specials 1964-1969 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-23-A. Television Commercial Testing at JWT, 1969 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-23.1-AB. Quickie Fact Sheets--Television Commercial Testing Services, 1969 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-24-ABCDEFGHI. Discussion of the Wearout of Television Commercials, 1970 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-25-ABC. Report on AMA Commercial Testing Conference, 1970 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-26-AB. Brief Fact Sheets--Television Commercial Testing Services, 1970 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-27-A. Evaluation of ARB and NSI Local Market Reports, 1970 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-28-ABCD. Television Commercial Evaluation at JWT: The CATV System, 1970 (Box R15)
    - X3.5-29-A. Television Commercial Testing at JWT, undated; 2 folders (Box R15)
    - X3.5-29.1-A. RCA-CSD--Why Television is Recommended as a Supplementary Medium for the Computer Division, 1970 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-30-AB. Review of Research on Television Communication Effectiveness, 1970 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-31-A. JWT Commercial Testing System, undated (Box R16)
    - X3.5-32-ABC. Exploration of Consumer Preferences for Commercial Break Scheduling in Televised Movies, 1980 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-33-ABC. Shogun Viewership Study, 1980 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-33.1-A. 10-Sec. Commercials Perspective, 1983 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-34-ABC. Split :30s: The Long and Short of It, 1984 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-34.1-AB. 15-Sec. Commercials: The Simple Truth, 1984 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-34.2-AB. Clutter and the Television Environment, 1984 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-35-AB. Super Bowl XIX Study, 1985 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-36-AB. 15-Sec. Commercials, 1985 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-37-A. Flippers: Changes in the Way that Americans Watch Television, 1986 (Box R16)
    - X3.5-38-AB. How Much Do Remote Control Devices Increase Flipping?, 1987 (Box R16)
    - X3.6-1. Drive-In Theaters as an Advertising Medium and Market, 1955 (Box R16)
    - X3.6-2. Report on Theater Advertising, 1959 (Box R16)
    - X3.7-1-ABC. Word-of-Mouth Communication, 1971 (Box R16)
    - X3.8-1.1. Report on Radio as an Advertising Medium, 1957 (Box R16)
    - X3.8-2-ABC. Radio Listening Habits and the Attitude of the U.S. Housewife, 1958 (Box R17)
    - X3.8-3-AB. Report on the Role of Radio in the Lives of U.S. Housewives, 1959 (Box R17)
    - X3.8-4. Radio Today, 1959 (Box R17)
    - X3.8-5. Report on Radio as an Advertising Medium, 1959 (Box R17)
    - X4-3-ABC. Consumer Incentives Study, undated (Box R17)
    - X4-4-AB. Promotional Merchandising 1959-1965 (Box R17)
    - X4-5-ABC. Behavioral Study of Consumer Incentives, 1969 (Box R17)
    - X4-6-ABC. Behavioral Study of Consumer Incentives, 1969 (Box R17)
    - X4-7-ABC. Incentive Study, 1969 (Box R17)
    - X4-8-A. Manufacturer's Price-Off Labels, 1978 (Box R17)
    - X4-9-AB. Tools in the Marketing Mix, 1978 (Box R17)
    - X4-10-A. How Grocery Stores Use Promotions, 1978 (Box R17)
    - X4.1-4-AB. Consumer Incentives, 1969 (Box R17)
    - X4.7-.1-A. Couponing Confidential, 1962 (Box R18)
    - X4.7-1. Couponing, 1965 (Box R18)
    - X4.7-1.1. Couponing, 1967 (Box R18)
    - X4.8-3-ABC. Packaging and Labeling, 1971 (Box R18)
    - X6-1. Evaluation of Product Acceptance, 1960 (Box R18)
    - X6-2. Practicum of Marketing Research, 1961; 3 folders (Box R18)
    - X6-4-ABC. Eldridge Marketing Plan, 1964 (Box R18)
    - X6-5-ABC. The 70s: A Marketing View, 1971 (Box R18)
    - X6-6-ABC. Developing Marketing/Advertising Approaches that Sell, 1975 (Box R19)
    - X6-7-A. Some Common Techniques in Marketing Research, 1975; 3 folders (Box R19)
    - X6-8-ABC. Demographic, Psychographics and Market Research, 1976 (Box R19)
    - X6-9-ABC. Getting Inside the Consumer's Head, 1976 (Box R19)
    - X6-10-AB. Project 118 (Consumers 1957-1977) (Box R19)
    - X6-11-ABC. In Pursuit of Happiness--The American Consumer Past, Present and Future, 1978 (Box R19)
    - X6-12-AB. Health Care and Leisure, 1977 (Box R19)
    - X6-13. Understanding Buyer Behavior, 1977-1978; 3 folders (Box R20)
    - X6-13.1-A. In Pursuit of Happiness, 1978 (Box R20)
    - X6-14-A. Demographics Study, 1979 (Box R20)
    - X6-15-ABC. Lifestyle Profile (U.S.), 1981 (Box R20)
    - X6-16-A. Consumer Financial Behavior, 1984 (Box R20)
    - X6-16-V1-V7. Shape '83--Impact of Health, Appearance and Fitness Concerns on Consumer Behavior, 1983; 2 folders (Box R20)
    - X6-16-V1-V7. Shape '83--Impact of Health, Appearance and Fitness Concerns on Consumer Behavior, 1983; 5 folders (Box R21)
    - X6.2-1-AB. Estimates and Projection of the U.S. Population, 1969 (Box R21)
    - X6.2-2-ABC. Middle America in the 80s, 1979 (Box R21)
    - X6.3-1. Attitudes Toward Canada in the U.S., 1964 (Box R21)
    - X6.3-2-A. The Philippine Market in 1970 (Box R21)
    - X6.3-2-A. The Philippine Market in 1970 (Box R22)
    - X6.3-3-A. Dew Toilet Soap--Karachi, 1964 (Box R22)
    - X6.3-4-A. Cosmetic Market--West Pakistan, 1964 (Box R22)
    - X6.3-5-A. Chesebrough Pond's Pakistan Advertising Recommendations, 1969-1970 (Box R22)
    - X6.3-6-A. Review of Color Television Ownership and Intention to Purchase (Canada), 1970 (Box R22)
    - X6.3-7-A. China 85 (removed to JWT Chicago Office Information Center Audiovisual Materials series), 1985 (Box R22)
    - X6.4-1-A. Evaluation of the Brass Rail Automatic Restaurant, 1963 (Box R22)
    - X6.4-2. Food Service Industry, 1966 (Box R22)
    - X6.4-3. Restaurant Study, 1972; 2 folders (Box R22)
    - X6.4-4-ABC. Trends in the Food Service Industry, 1977 (Box R22)
    - X6.5-2-ABC. Population and Retail Sales Estimates, 1956 (Box R22)
    - X6.5-3. Review of Available Information on 20 U.S. Metropolitan Markets, 1961 (Box R22)
    - X6.5-3.1. Changing Consumer in Our Emerging Society, 1960 (Box R23)
    - X6.6-.2. Report on Food Stores, Private Brands and Cooperative Advertising, 1954 (Box R23)
    - X6.6-1-V1-V3. National and Regional Corporate Chains, undated; 3 folders (Box R23)
    - X6.6-2-V4. National and Regional Corporate Chains, undated; 2 folders (Box R23)
    - X6.6-3.1. Future Patterns in Food Retailing, 1956 (Box R23)
    - X6.6-4-ABC. How to Compute Rent on a Square Foot of Shelf Space, 1957 (Box R23)
    - X6.6-5-ABC. Retail Grocery Chain Buying Committee Deliberations, 1957 (Box R23)
    - X6.6-6-ABC. Deliberations of a Chain Grocery Buying Committee, 1957 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-6.1. Analysis of the Vending Industry, 1964 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-7-A. Top 90 U.S. Markets Study of Food Stores, 1958 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-8. Rockville Center Shopping Survey, 1958 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-8.1-ABC. The Public and the Drug Store, 1958 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-8.2. Nonfoods in Supermarkets, 1964 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-8.3. New Era in Food Retailing, 1965 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-9. The Smaller Retailer and His Suppliers, 1959 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-10-ABC. Consumers' Mart of America, 1959 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-11. New Revolution in Distribution, 1961 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-12-ABC. Grocery Store Buyers and Advertising, 1959 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-13. Discount Centers, 1962 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-14-A. Some Determinants of Helping Behavior in a Field Setting, 1970 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-15-A. Lodging Industry Competitive Advertising Report, 1975 (Box R24)
    - X6.6-15-A. Lodging Industry Competitive Advertising Report, 1975 (Box R25)
    - X6.6-16-A. Today's New Shoppers: Men and Working Women, 1984 (Box R25)
    - X6.6-17-A. Overview of Scanner Services, 1986 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-2-A. American Soup Industry, 1955 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-3. Study of Innovators, 1960 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-4-ABC. Study of Innovation: Knorr Soups, 1961 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-5-ABC. Proposed JWT New Products Monitoring Service, 1969 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-7-AB. Researching New Products, 1974 (Box R25)
    - X6.7-8-A. New Product Model, 1978 (Box R25)
    - X6.8-1-A. Marketing to the DIY Consumer in the 1980s, 1984 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-1-ABC. The Negro American Market (includes sample of ads), 1956-1963 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-1.1-A. Negro Population, 1956 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-2-ABC. Negro Market Presentation, 1956 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-2.1. Negro Immigrant and Business Enterprise, 1957 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-3. Brief Summary of Negro Market and Media Data, 1960 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-4-ABC. A Look at the Negro Market, 1960 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-5-ABC. Negro Market I: Negro Lifestyle, 1962 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-5.1. Urban Negro Market, 1965 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-6-ABC. Negro Market II: Negroes and Media, 1962 (Box R25)
    - X6.81-7-ABC. Negro Market III: Negro Attitudes Toward Food, 1963 (Box R26)
    - X6.81-8-ABC. Proposal for a JWT Chicago Seminar on Advertising to the Black Consumer, 1970 (Box R26)
    - X6.81-9-ABC. Advertising and Black America, 1973 (Box R26)
    - X6.81-11-AB. Qualitative Exploration of Black Female Consumer Attitudes, 1981 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-3-ABC. The Teenage Market, 1956 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-3.1-A. Influences of Children's Advertising on Brand Preferences, 1960 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-4. How to Win Children and Influence Mother, 1965 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-5-AB. Researching Children, 1969 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-6-A. Research Study: Flintstones Chewable Vitamins, 1970 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-7-A. Use of Individual Interview Techniques on Young Children, 1970 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-8-A. Chocks and Flintstones Television Commercial Testing, 1970 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-9-A. Purposes, Patterns and Protection in a Campus Drug-Using Community, 1970 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-9.2-ABC. Children's Television Programming and Advertising, 1972 (Box R26)
    - X6.82-10-ABC. Advertising to Children, 1972 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-11-A. Today's Child, 1976 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-12-ABC. Communicating with Children, 1981 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-13-AB. Seminar on Marketing to Children and Their Parents, 1982 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-14-AB. Researching Children, 1983 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-15-A. Advertising to Children, undated (Box R27)
    - X6.82-16-ABCD. U.S. Teenage Market, 1983 (Box R27)
    - X6.82-16.1-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1983; 2 folders (Box R27)
    - X6.82-16.1-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1983; 2 folders (Box R28)
    - X6.82-16.2-A. Youth Attitude Tracking Study, 1983 (Box R28)
    - X6.82-16.3-A. Youth Attitude Tracking Study, 1984; 2 folders (Box R28)
    - X6.82-17-AB. U.S. Teenage Market, 1984 (Box R28)
    - X6.82-17.1-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1984 (Box R28)
    - X6.82-17.2-AB. U.S. Teenage Market, 1984 (Box R28)
    - X6.82-17.3-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1984; 3 folders (Box R29)
    - X6.82-18-A. Teenage Economic Power 1983, 1984 (Box R29)
    - X6.82-19-A. Marketing Characteristics of Young Singles in the U.S. (20-35 year-olds), 1985 (Box R29)
    - X6.82-20-ABC. U.S. Teenage Market, 1985 (Box R29)
    - X6.82-21-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1985 (Box R29)
    - X6.82-21.1-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1985 (Box R30)
    - X6.82-21.2-A. Child Care Factbook, 1986 (Box R30)
    - X6.82-21.3-A. Children's Research Suppliers and Methods, 1986 (Box R30)
    - X6.82-22-A. U.S. Teenage Market, 1986; 2 folders (Box R30)
    - X6.82-23-A. Teenage Economic Power, 1984 (Box R30)
    - X6.82-24-A. Teenage Economic Power, 1985 (Box R30)
    - X6.83-4-ABC. Marketing Profile of the Senior Citizen Group, 1957 (Box R30)
    - X6.83-5-A. Old Age Market with Special Reference to the Restaurant Business, 1978 (Box R30)
    - X6.83-6-A. Retirement Living Factbook, 1986 (Box R30)
    - X6.84-1-Part 1. On Setting Up a Home: Memorandum on Newlyweds, 1959 (Box R30)
    - X6.84-1-Part 2. Setting Up Housekeeping: Study of Newly Married Young Women, 1959 (Box R30)
    - X6.84-2-A. Setting Up Housekeeping, 1959 (Box R30)
    - X6.84-3-ABC. The Seventies: Decade of the Young Marrieds, 1969 (Box R31)
    - X6.84-4. Socio-Economic/Psychographical/Lifestyle Profile of Men 18-34, 1983 (Box R31)
    - X6.84-5. The Singles Market, 1986 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-1-ABC. Marketing to Men: Personal Care, 1963 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-2-ABC. Marketing for Men: Food, 1964 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-3-ABC. Marketing for Men: Food, 1964 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-4. Marketing Foods to Men, 1965 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-5-A. Mrs. Middle Majority, 1965 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-6-ABC. The Housewife I: Young Mothers (18-34, not employed), 1965 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-7-ABC. The Housewife II: The Working Housewife, 1965 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-7.1-ABC. The Housewife III: Mothers (35-44), 1966 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-7.2-ABC. The Housewife IV: Mature Housewives (45-60), 1966 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-7.3-ABC. The Housewife V: Young Women (16-20, prior to marriage), 1966 (Box R31)
    - X6.85-8. Housewife Study: Young Mothers, 1965 (Box R31)
    - X6.86-1. The Spanish Speaking Market in the U.S., 1968 (Box R31)
    - X6.86-2-ABC. Advertising to the Hispanic Consumer, 1980 (Box R32)
    - X6.86-3-A. Analysis of Hispanic Data, 1980 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-1-A. Proposal to "Publish" a Test Market Fact Book, 1969 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-2-A. 61 Test Markets, 1970 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-3-A. Test Market Evaluation Bulletin, 1970 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-4-A. Is Test Marketing the Best Sales Prediction Tool?, 1973 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-5-B. Test Marketing, 1974 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-6-A. Test Marketing, 1974 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-7-ABCD. Estimating Sales for New Product Introduction, 1978 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-8-A. Test Marketing, 1979 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-9-A. Laboratory Test Market Methodologies, 1980 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-10-ABC. New Product Information, 1980 (Box R32)
    - X6.87-11-A. Test Marketing Guide Book, 1988; 2 folders (Box R32)
    - X6.88-1-A. Military Market Data Book, 1976 (Box R33)
    - X6.88-2-A. Military Market Data Book, 1979 (Box R33)
    - X7-1-A. Guidelines for the Use of the 1968 MRCA Menu Census Data, 1969 (Box R33)
    - X7-2. Final Report on Video Publishing, 1979 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-3. Status Report on Prepared Frozen Foods, 1957 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-4-ABC. Estimated Consumption of Food in the U.S. 1960-1965, 1956 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-5-ABC. The Confections Industry, 1958 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-6-ABC. General Memorandum on Spices, Condiments and Seasonings, 1960 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-7-ABC. Attitudes Toward Lunch, 1960 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-8-AB. Brand Image Concepts Evaluation Program, 1961 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-8.1. Consumption of Shellfish-Shrimp Among Restaurants and Hotels in the U.S., 1961 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-9-A. Comparison of Four Questioning Techniques: Brand Preferences and Evaluation, 1961 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-10. Cooking Attitudes and Behaviour (U.K.), 1961 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-11-ABC. Instant Tea: Its Image and Uses, 1963 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-12-ABC. Notes on Tape-Recorded Interviews About Instant Tea, 1963 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-13-A. A Qualitative Study of Attitudes Toward Instant Tea, 1963 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-14-A. Attitudes Toward Instant Tea, 1963 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-15-ABC. A Study on Consumer Acceptance of Canned Meat, 1964 (Box R33)
    - X7.1-16-ABC. The Outlook of Mrs. M.M. Cook in Feeding Her Family 1950-1955, 1965 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-17. Consumer Expenditures for Grocery Items and Selected Household Products, 1965 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-18-A. Making Aunt Jemima Pancakes, 1966 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-19-A. Buying and Using Like, 1966 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-20-A. Makin' Bacon, 1968 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-20.1-A. Consumer Response to the "Tastes Like Daddy Food" Strategy for Beech Nut Baby Foods, 1968 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-20.2-A. An Exploration of Consumer Response to "Daddy Food" Creative Strategy, 1968 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-21-A. Sour Dextrose Candy Study, 1969 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-22-ABC. The Bottled Water Market: An Overview, 1969 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-23-A. Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Breakfast, 1970 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-23.1-A. The U.K. Market for Shandy (JWT London), 1970 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-24-A. Commentary on the Dairy Products Market, 1970 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-25-A. U.S. Market for Dehydrated Potatoes and Dried Vegetables, 1970 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-26-C. Mealtime and the Consumer, 1971 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-27-A. Pineapple Growers Association Advertising and Promotion Test, 1971 (Box R34)
    - X7.1-30-B. JWT Creative Research Report #1: Nutrition and Family, 1973 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-30.1-A. The Current Status of the Soy Protein Market in the U.S., 1974 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-31-A. The Textured Vegetable Protein Market, 1975 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-31.1-A. Tea Industry Briefing Report, 1977 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-31.2-AB. Private Label Trends, 1977 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-32-ABC. Proposed Jewel Generic Study, 1978 (Box R35)
    - X7.1-33-ABC. The Moveable Feast: America's Evolving Concepts of Food 1950-1980, 1978; 4 folders (Box R35)
    - X7.1-33.1-A. Private Label Trend Report, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-33.2-A. Private Label Study, 1978 (Box R36)
    - X7.1-33.3-A. Unbranded Food Product Study, 1978; 2 folders (Box R36)
    - X7.1-33.4-A. Consumer Reaction to Jewel (Food Stores) Generic Products, 1978; 2 folders (Box R36)